mwave.com.au 2018-05-09

# Customer Service Help & Support Centre | Mwave.com.au

##  Privacy Policy

This privacy statement has been updated to reflect the recent changes to the Australian Privacy Laws as of the 12th March 2014 in relation to how organisations that collect personal or sensitive data must do so in compliance with the Australian Privacy Principles (APP) 

Mwave has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for this website: Mwave.com.au. Any changes or updates to our privacy practices will be updated through our website. If you have questions or concerns regarding this statement, please e-mail us at [sales@mwave.com.au](mailto:sales@mwave.com.au)

**We respect your privacy**

At Mwave, we value our customers and their privacy. All personal information is used to ensure efficient processing of your order. This information is used by our staff for contacting and identifying customers and their needs. We will not sell, rent, or loan any identifiable personal information to any third party, unless we are legally required to do so. 

**No SPAMMING!**

Unsolicited, "spam" mail is not sent to Mwave's customers. The only email customers will receive, are updates to their recent or past orders, updates to company policy, updates and news to Mwave website, Surveys about Mwave Customer Service and occasional promotions (if requested). Mwave is not responsible for information and actions by third party individuals/companies who have received information from customer's directly. 

**Registration**

Our site's registration form requires users to give us contact information (your name, email address and phone numbers). The customer's contact information is used to contact the visitor in the event of a problem when processing an order. For example, problems with credit card verification, product availability, etc. Users have a choice of receiving future mailings; during the registration process. 

Our site uses an order form for customers to request information, products, and services. We collect visitor's contact information and financial information (credit card numbers only when using this form of payment). The customer's contact information is used to communicate with the visitor when necessary. i.e, in the event there is a problem processing an order, corporate changes, or policy changes. Financial information that is collected is used to bill the user for products and services. The customer ID numbers are assigned to Web site visitors to verify the user's identity and for use as account numbers in our record system. 

**Anonymity and pseudonymity**

Our site allows you to remain anonymous or use an alias when making a general enquiry about our services and products through email, online chat or the ticket system. 

However, we require disclosure of identity/ personal information in order to facilitate enquiries about your orders, warranty claims etc placed with us. We will not disclose to any unidentified person/s information regarding orders or contact information or disclose to customers order information relating to other customers. 

**Security of Personal Information**  
Mwave uses the industry standard security protocol Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) to encode sensitive information like your credit card number that passes between you and Mwave. We employ the latest 128-bit encryption technology in all areas of the site which require you to provide your personal or account information. This means that the credit card information you send is encrypted by your computer, and then decrypted again on our side, preventing others from accessing your private information in between. So, when using an SSL capable browser, shopping on Mwave web site is perfectly safe. 

While on a secure page, such as our order form, the lock icon on the bottom of Web browsers such as Netscape Navigator and Microsoft Internet Explorer becomes locked, as opposed to un-locked, or open, when you are just surfing. 

Mwave is the sole collector of information, and is not shared with any 3rd parties. However, we do offer printable rebate forms and warranty information. Mwave is not responsible for the privacy practices of those companies. Please review their respective privacy statements. 

While we use SSL encryption to protect sensitive information online, we also do everything in our power to protect user-information off-line. All of our users’ information, not just the sensitive information mentioned above, is restricted in our offices. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, our billing clerk or a customer service representative) are granted access to personally identifiable information. Our employees must use password-protected screen-savers when they leave their desk. When they return, they must re-enter their password to re-gain access to your information. Furthermore, ALL employees are kept up-to-date on our security and privacy practices. Every quarter, as well as any time new policies are added, our employees are notified and/or reminded about the importance we place on privacy, and what they can do to ensure our customers’ information is protected. Finally, the servers that we store personally identifiable information on are kept in a secure environment. 

We provide to our shipping partners your contact information to facilitate the delivery of your order only and for no other reason. Our shipping partners are obligated by Privacy Laws to handle your personal information accordingly. 

**Links/3rd Parties**   
This site contains links to other sites. Mwave is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this Web site. 

If you have any questions about the security at our web site, please send an e-mail to [sales@mwave.com.au](mailto:sales@mwave.com.au)

**Removal/Opt Out/Unsubscribe**   
Our site provides users the opportunity to opt-out of receiving marketing communications from us at the point where we request information about the visitor. 

This site gives users the following options for removing their information from our database to not receive future communications or to no longer receive our service. You can send email to: [sales@mwave.com.au](mailto:sales@mwave.com.au)

**Correct/Update**  
This site gives users the following options for changing and modifying information previously provided.   
web site: Update/Modify Account Information   
email: [sales@mwave.com.au](mailto:sales@mwave.com.au)

**Notification of Changes**  
If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on here so our users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under circumstances, if any, we disclose it. If at any point we decide to use personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time it was collected, we will notify users by way of an email. Users will have a choice as to whether or not we use their information in this different manner. We will use information in accordance with the privacy policy under which the information was collected. 

**Complaints / Questions**  
If you would like to submit a complaint regarding a breach by Mwave or have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact Mwave: [sales@mwave.com.au](mailto:sales@mwave.com.au)
